agorics.com 2013-03-18

# Privacy Policy

#### Agorics Privacy Policy

Agorics has outlined its strategy to safeguard the personal information of its users and clients in the section, Privacy Policy.  It is all being explained in this section how Agorics collects this information, uses it and protects the privacy of this personal information being provided by its users and clients. Anyone who logs on to this site or uses its services has to abide by the terms of this privacy policy specifically being given by Agorics. In this context, the activities of the third parties involved do not come under the privacy policy outlines of Agorics.

#### The information Agorics collects

Certain information gets to be automatically recorded in the server logs of agorics when anyone one logs on to www.agorics.com. this includes the IP address of the visitor, the IP address along with the URL of the website that has sent the visitor to http://www.agorics.com, browser cookie and browser type. The nature of the information further expands when the visitor decides to use the services being offered by Agorics by getting registered to this website. In this case, Agorics demands information like the user’s name, cell phone number, cell phone device information and network carrier information. Some optional requirement is also there like the email address, gender, age and the location of the user that solely depends upon the willingness of that person if that person wants to share this information or not. In case, the visitor log on to http://www.agorics.com from his cell phone device, then Agorics does also collect cell phone device identification information.

On the voyage to this website, when you lands upon the, main page of this site, cookies get to be sent to your computer that mean to identify your browser. These cookies can be session cookies and the persistent cookies. Some of the advertisers at Agorics can also use these cookies but we at Agorics do not take the responsibility of the usage of those cookies. Though, you can manage the cookies from your browser but still we recommend you to leave them in an activated condition. Our registered members have the facility to invite their friends and acquaintances to this website and for this purpose; they need to submit the email addresses of those people. Agorics guarantees not to use those emails for selling or advertising purposes.

We at Agorics do not intend to sell the personal information being provided by our valued users and visitors to any third party without their own consent and willingness.

#### How Agorics uses your personal information

Agorics uses this personal information being provided by you so that it can maintain and operate the website and provide different features and functionalities of this website to all those who come to visit this website. Cell phone number is being used to let you receive that content and material that you request. It is guaranteed that this number along with your email address will not be used for marketing or advertising purposes without your consent where you will be having the ability to opt in or to opt out. The basic purpose of gathering this personally identifiable and certain non-personally identifiable information is basically to test the marketing stratagem of our campaign and to assess the total aggregate like total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. and this information is not required to resubmit when you log on for the next time. It gets recorded and identified automatically whenever you log on to http://www.agorics.com.

Though, one thing should be kept in mind that the information being disclosed by you online becomes a part of your public profile page which can be used and advertised by others. And, Agorics can use the suggestions and comments being posted in discussions in the public areas for promotional or marketing purposes because the users by commenting in such places gives the  irrevocable, transferable and royalty-free license to Agorics to transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and reformat and otherwise use such public Information.

Third party advertisers who advertise their ads when you visit our website may use your personal information excluding your name and contact details so that they can provide you with more advertisements related to he services of your interest in future.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Agorics does not intend to sell rent or advertise your personal information without your own willingness and consent. There are some conditions where the disclosure of this personal information become necessary such as conforming to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Agorics, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Agorics Terms of Use or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.  Agorics also owns the rights to transfer this personal information if a new entity takes over the current entity of Agorics.

#### Security of Your Personal Information

For the purpose of privacy and security of your account information, Agorics allots you a password. You need to cut off the unauthorized access to your account by logging off after having used a shared computer. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your personal information during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input.

#### Your ability to edit your Account Information and Preferences

You can edit or correct your personal information along with profile and email preferences. For the purpose of security and privacy, a unique pass word is requested by Agorics if you decide to make certain amendments and changes in your personal and profile information. Though, your personal information s bound to stay with us once it gets to be recorded in our server log, even after you decide to delete your account at http://www.agorics.com.

#### International Users

Agorics website is being hosted in united states of America but if you are a user from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, you are required to give your consent to the transfer of your information to the united states if you want to have the continued use of this website.

#### Links to other sites

We may put the links of other websites and products on our website. But, you should keep in mind if you try to use their services or products, you need to abide by the privacy policy of that third party not that of Agorics. You need to review their policies before you decide to visit or use their services. Agorics does not own the responsibility of the privacy policy and security functions of those websites.

#### Children under age 13

Agorics does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age and this is the reason, no section of our website is meant for persona under 13. In case, you are 13 or below, you are not to access or use Agorics website and services.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Agorics has all the rights to make certain changes in its privacy policy from time to time at its sole discretion. But, we will surly post these changes on the websites and our uses and visitors will be required to revisit that privacy policy page to remain informed f the current terms and conditions of privacy policy. Use of the personal information is subject to the privacy policy of the time when we decide to use that information.

#### Conditions of Use

In case, you visit or decide to use the Agorics services, your use and visit to this website will be under the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, including implementation of California law, limitations on damages and arbitration of disputes.

#### Questions about our Privacy Policy

You are requested to contact us at  [support@agorics.com](mailto:support@agorics.com) , in case you have further questions and concerns regarding our privacy policy.
